# MUHAMMAD ANAS AFZAAL

B-185 Saghir Centre, Block-16 F.B Area, Karachi.

Phone: +(92)312 3616359 Email: anaskhan.all95@gmail.com

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Software Developer - Aimviz (March 2022 - Present)

**Responsibilities:** Development, optimization, and, maintenance of Web Applications.

**Technologies & Skills:** Angular, JavaScript, TypeScript, ASP.NET, MSSQL, C#, HTML, CSS, SCSS, Bootstrap.

### Front end Developer – Symits (September 2020 – February 2022)

**Responsibilities:** Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites.

**Technologies & Skills:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify and, Adobe Photoshop.

# Front end Developer – Optimal Creations (March 2020 – August 2020)

**Responsibilities:** Development, optimization, and, maintenance of WordPress and custom websites and content writing for websites and social media marketing.

**Technologies & Skills:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, PHP, jQuery, WordPress, Shopify.

### **EDUCATION**

- Masters of Computer Science (MCS) University of Karachi (2021– Present )
- ➤ Bachelors of Computer Science (BCS) University of Karachi (2016 2019)
- ➤ Intermediate (Pre-Engineering) D.J Science College (2012 2014)
- ➤ Matriculation (Computer Science) Metropolitan Academy ( 2000 2012 )

### SUMMARY

I am a Frontend Developer who understands and manages the user interface according to the users' needs and the best of the experience.

I have core expertise in the latest technologies and trends such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, jQuery, Angular, React, C#, SQL name a few.

## LINKS

Portfolio

LinkedIn.

### SKILLS

avaScript:	
Angular:	
ГуреScript:	
Query:	
C#:	
SQL:	
Git:	
HTML:	
CSS:	
SCSS:	
ASP.NET:	
VordPress:	
Poact.	